Finding Aid for American Friends Service Committee. Michigan Area Office records, 1956-2002
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Peace Education Committee
  - MAPEC Coordinator/Peace Secretary, Richard Cleaver, files 1982-1992
    - Non-Violence
      - Movement Action Plan 1991 (Box 6)
      - Non-Violent Direct Action, training, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Organizations dedicated to Non-Violence 1984-1992 (Box 6)
      - Sharp, Gene, Albert Einstein Institute, speaking tour 1990 (Box 6)
      - Women's speaking tour on U.S. Military Bases (Box 6)
    - Civil Disobedience
      - Background material (Box 6)
      - Civilian-Based Defense Association Conference, Windsor 1992 (Box 6)
      - Adapt, Michigan Chapter (Box 6)
    - Homophobia
      - Homophobia workshop materials (Box 6)
      - Homophobia workshops, 5 folders (Box 6)
      - Campaign to End Homophobia 1991 (Box 6)
      - "A Certain Terror, Homophobia, Oppression and Violence" 1991 (Box 6)
      - A Certain Terror written by RC and distributed commercially, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
        (sampling of invoices for booklet only)
    - Lesbian/Gay
      - Workshops and Conferences
        - AFSC 1991 Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual Consultation, 3 folders (Box 6)
        - AIDS Project 1989 (Box 6)
        - Call for Unity between Peace and Lesbian/Gay Movements 1988 (Box 6)
        - "Changing Men's Roles in a Changing World" 1985 (Box 6)
        - "Ending Men's Violence", 15th Conference on Men and Masculinity 1990 (Box 6)
        - "Exploring Gay Issues" 1983 (Box 6)
        - Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity 1994 (Box 6)
        - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights 1987, 2 folders (Box 6)
          (includes background material and civil disobedience material)
        - Pride Week, Civil Disobedience Workshop 1988 (Box 6)
        - "Touched and Be Changed, Change and Be Alive", Chicago conference 1988, 2 folders (Box 6)
          (includes Immersion Experience, ALC packet as background material)
      - Topical file
        - Anti-Gay violence at MSU (Box 7)
        - Bridges of Respect, Creating Support for Lesbian and Gay Youth 1990 (Box 7)
        - Domestic Partnership Ordinance (Ann Arbor) 1991 (Box 7)
        - Sodomy Law Challenge 1988 (Box 7)
        - Stonewall Summer 1989 (Box 7)
    - Middle East Peace Education Topical File
      - Awad, Mubarek and Nancy Nye 1990 (Box 7)
      - Birzeit University (Box 7)
      - Gulf War, Lessons Learned from, Aquinas Forum 1991 (Box 7)
      - Gvul, Yesh tour 1988 (Box 7)
      - Libyan Indictments 1991 (Box 7)
      - Low Density Conflict (Box 7)
      - Middle East Peace Education, Annual Review, national 1988 (Box 7)
      - Middle East Peace Notes, 1984-1992 (scattered), 5 folders (Box 7)
        (RC wrote extensively for this quarterly publication; also includes correspondence from regional MEPN Committee)
      - Nunn, Maxine Kaufmann 1989 (Box 7)
      - Quakers and the PLO, "Jewish News" interview of RC 1991 (Box 7)
      - Palestinian Aid Society (Box 7)
      - Palestinian National Council Resolution 1988 (Box 7)
      - Persian Gulf, teach-in, to oppose 1988 (Box 7)
      - Shahak, Israel (Box 7)
      - West Banks Settlements, statement 1982-1983 (Box 7)
      - "Who's Next? U.S. Militarism and the Lessons of the Gulf War "
        - Position paper prepared by RC 1991 (Box 7)
        - "U.S. Militarism, Who's Next?" (topic of speech by Jay Hathaway) 1991 (Box 7)
        - Talks by RC on "Who's Next?" 1992, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - MAPEC Coordinator Jan Wright, files 1993-2002
    - MAPEC Minutes, program planning 1993-2002, 8 folders (Box 7)
    - Grant from the H.O.P.E Fund, Community Foundation for Southeastern Michigan 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Marriage Legislation 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    - Programming Planning Cycles 1994-2001 (Box 7)
    - Workshops and Conferences
      - AFSC Chicago National Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Gathering 1997, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Bridges Project for Gay and Lesbian Youth 1995, 2 folders (Box 8)
        (includes training manual for LYRIC Youth Talkline)
      - "Building Bridges for an Inclusive Church" 1995 (Box 8)
      - "Creating Opportunities" 1995 (Box 8)
      - "Day of Vigilance" 1999 (Box 8)
      - Dialog, Adrian Training School 1997 (Box 8)
      - Faith in Action 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - GLSEN Midwest Conference 1998, 3 folders (Box 8)
        (with background materials)
      - "In the Life: A Cultural Celebration of the Black Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Community" 1999 (Box 8)
      - Interfaith Organizing in Michigan (Box 8)
      - Opening Hearts and Minds, workshop notebook presented by Love Makes A Family, Inc. (Box 8)
      - Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (P-FLAG) 1996, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - "The Flower on the Lily Pad". AFSC's Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender programming 1998 (Hawaii) (Box 8)
      - Toward Understanding; Education and Nonviolent Dialogue about Sexual Orientation, 1995-2001, 7 folders (Box 8)
        (includes workshop manual, participant packets, workshop series, speaker training program)
      - Transgender Resources, Pacific Region (Box 8)
      - Transgender resources, Pacific Mountain Region (Box 8)
      - Unity Rally for Racial Justice 1997 (Box 8)
      - "Voices of Hope: Lesbians and Gays in the Church" 1999 (Box 8)
      - Women's Dialogue: Building Community in the Face of Violence 1995 (Box 8)
    - Topical file
      - Affirmative Action and prohibition of gay marriages 1996 (Box 8)
      - Cost of Prisoner Phone Calls 1999 (Box 8)
      - Godchaux's Resolution 1997 (Box 8)
      - Gay Lesbian issues (Box 8)
      - Green Pastures Quarterly Meeting 1999 (Box 8)
      - "Justice in a Time of Broken Bones" 2001 (Box 8)
        (position paper on hate crimes and hate violence)
      - Michigan Ballot Initiative 1994 (Box 8)
      - Positions of religious bodies on Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual issues 1996 (Box 8)
      - Clippings (Box 8)
      - Kalamazoo anti-gay ballot initiative 2001 (Box 8)
      - Mailing and reports 1994 (Box 8)
      - Freedom to Marry 1996 (Box 8)
      - Ypsilanti non-discrimination ordinance 1998 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
- Community Relations Committee Program Files
  The Community Relations Committee series is of most value for its documentation of MAO's involvement in the topic of Criminal Justice, especially in such areas as bail and other pretrial issues, community-based corrections, the death penalty, prison alternatives, prison overcrowding, just treatment of prisoners, and positive reintegration of prisoners into society (the Options Center). Included in these materials are files of correspondence between AFSC staff and prisoners. This correspondence documents the MACRC's commitment to working with prisoners to ensure their equitable treatment within the criminal justice system.
  - Administrative
    - Minutes 1969-1987, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports 1963-1987, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Secretary's Monthly Reports 1973-1977 (Box 9)
    - Dayton Regional Office (DRO) 1981 (Box 9)
    - Detroit Anti-Hunger Committee
      - Minutes 1975 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence 1975 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Papers 1975 (Box 9)
      - Institutional Service Units 1971, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Program Fliers and Brochures 1977-1982 (partial) (Box 9)
    - Program Review 1984-1985 (Box 9)
    - Staff Reports 1978-1986 (partial) (Box 9)
    - Telephone Federal Tax Withholding Information (Box 9)
    - Writings 1980-1985 (Box 9)
  - Programs / Topics
    - Criminal Justice
      - Bail
        - Community Bail Organization 1973 (Box 9)
        - Community Bail Services, Program Proposal 1974-1976 (Box 9)
        - Court Case: People v. Spicer (Regarding constitutionality of pretrial release system) 1976 (Box 9)
        - Legislation
          - Constitutional Amendment Proposal (Regarding denial of bail) 1976 (Box 9)
          - General Court Rule 790 (Regarding 10% deposit bond) 1977-1979 (Box 9)
          - House Bill 6056 (Regarding bail), 1974 (Box 9)
          - Kelley Ruling (Regarding 10% bond deposit) 1974 (Box 9)
          - Pretrial Release act 1974 (Box 9)
          - Senate Bill 17 (Regarding regulation of bondsmen) 1979 (Box 9)
          - Senate Bill 99 (Regarding regulation of bondsmen) 1977 (Box 9)
          - Senate Bill 1039 (Regarding regulation of bondsmen) 1976 (Box 9)
          - Senate Bill 1212 (Bail reform) 1974 (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence Regarding Release on Recognizance 1971-1977 (Box 9)
        - Washtenaw Community Bail Fund (WCBF)
          - Articles of Incorporation 1975 (Box 9)
          - Board of Directors, Minutes 1980 (partial) (Box 9)
          - Case of Ricky Bullock (Bond) 1976-1979 (Box 9)
          - Correspondence 1976-1982, 3 folders (Box 9)
          - Contributors 1975-1976 (Box 9)
          - Court Cases 1977-1978 (Box 9)
          - Funding Applications 1977-1978 (Box 9)
          - Legal Documents 1977-1981 (Box 9)
          - Minutes 1974-1978 (Box 9)
          - Miscellaneous Administrative 1974-1976 (Box 9)
          - Printed Materials 1977-1980 (Box 9)
          - Quality Improvement Project 1978 (Box 9)
          - Training Manual circa 1977 (Box 9)
      - Community-Based Corrections
        - Corrections and the Community Project 1978-1979 (Box 10)
        - Community Corrections Act 1980 (Box 10)
        - Paper: Marc Mauer, "The Movement Toward Community-Based Corrections in the U.S.: Social and Historical Perspectives," circa 1975 (Box 10)
      - Correspondence
        - In 1977-1978 (Box 10)
        - Out 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Death Penalty
        - Clippings 1982-1986, 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Correspondence 1979-1987 (Box 10)
        - Michigan Coalition Against the Death Penalty (MCADP)
          - Coordinator's Report 1985-1986 (Box 10)
          - Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 10)
          - Fundraising 1985-1986 (Box 10)
          - Law Enforcement Survey Undated (Box 10)
          - Legal Papers 1985 (Box 10)
          - Newsletter 1985-1986 (Box 10)
          - Steering/Executive Committee, Minutes 1981-1986 scattered, 2 folders (Box 10)
          - Washtenaw Coalition, Minutes 1985-1986 (Box 10)
        - Position Statements (Regarding death penalty)
          - American Friends Service Committee 1976-1977 (Box 10)
          - Attorneys 1982 (Box 10)
          - Politicians 1981-1985 (Box 10)
          - United Auto Workers (UAW) and National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) 1985 (Box 10)
      - Michigan Council on Crime and Delinquency 1985 (Box 10)
      - Michigan Prison Disturbances Task Force 1981 (Box 10)
      - People United for Justice 1976 (Box 10)
      - Pretrial Justice
        - Citizen's Information Service 1972-1973 (Box 10)
        - Citizens for Pretrial Justice (CPJ)
          - Goldfarb and Mitchell Case (Regarding illegal bondsmen practices) 1973-1984 (Box 10)
          - Minutes 1973-1976 (partial) (Box 10)
            (includes some minutes of Ad hoc Bail Committee)
          - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Statements 1973-1975 (Box 10)
        - Paper: Nancy Margolis and Marc Mauer, "Organizing for Pretrial Justice: A Community Education Process Model," 1975 (Box 10)
      - Prison Alternatives
        - Coalition Against More Prisons 1981 (Box 10)
        - Correspondence In 1979-1986 (Box 10)
        - Michigan Coalition for Prison Alternatives 1977-1978 (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous Statements and Correspondence 1980s (Box 10)
        - Resolution/Michigan League for Human Services 1979 (Box 10)
        - Sentencing Project 1984-1987 (Box 10)
      - Prison Overcrowding
        - Michigan Coalition for Prison Alternatives Newsletter: "Instead of Prisons," 1978-1986, 4 folders (Box 10)
        - Michigan Prison Overcrowding Project (MI-POP)
          - Constituency Building
            - 1982-1984 (Box 10)
            - Budget/Planning 1982-1983 (Box 10)
          - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Statements 1983-1984 (Box 10)
          - Surveys 1984-1986 (Box 10)
        - Milliken Proposal (Regarding prison construction) 1979 (Box 10)
        - Parole Reform
          - Parolee Registration 1981 (Box 10)
          - Proposal B 1978 (Box 10)
        - Proposal E 1980 (Box 10)
      - Options Center (Helping prisoners re-assimilate into society)
        - Board Minutes 1983-1986 (Box 10)
        - Feasibility Subcommittee 1983-1984 (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous Reports and Minutes 1982-1987 (Box 10)
        - Statement: Marc Mauer, Regarding the Prisoners Overcrowding Emergency Act of October 1983 (Box 10)
      - Prison
        - Huron Valley Women's Facility 1977-1986 (Box 10)
        - Milan Letters 1981-1985 (Box 10)
        - Prison Riot Letters (riot at Jackson State Prison) 1981 (Box 10)
        - Prisoner Visitation and Support 1979-1986, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Prisoners' Progress Association 1978 (Box 11)
        - Women Lifers 1981 (Box 11)
      - Justice and prisons (miscellaneous programs and papers) (Box 11)
      - Update Packet (Mailers) 1981-1986 (partial) (Box 11)
    - National Criminal Justice Program
      - National Administration of Justice Programs 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - National Justice Task Force
        - Report of Justice Task Force 1976 (Box 11)
        - Formation and minutes 1977 (Box 11)
        - Perspective on AFSC Criminal Justice Programs, 1978 (Box 11)
      - National Criminal Justice Panel Minutes 1979-1986, 10 folders (Box 11)
      - Justice Gathering 1982 (Box 11)
    - Criminal Justice Update Packets (Marc Mauer) 1981-1986, 14 folders (Box 11)
    - Regional Criminal Justice Programs
      - Dayton 1982-1986, 6 folders (Box 11)
      - Flushing, New York (Box 12)
      - Hawaii (Box 12)
      - New England 1980-1986, 3 folders (Box 12)
      - New York City (Box 12)
      - Northern California 1975-1990, 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Pasadena (Box 12)
      - St. Louis (Box 12)
    - Death Penalty
      - Amnesty International Memorandum to President Clinton 2000 (Box 12)
      - Articles and reports on the death penalty 1981-2001, 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Church Positions against death penalty 1985-1999 (Box 12)
      - Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty 1997 (Box 12)
      - Death Row
        - Death Row Inmates
          - Alan J. Bannister (Box 12)
          - Articles and messages (Box 12)
          - Mentally ill (Box 12)
          - Native Americans (Box 12)
          - Texas inmates (Box 12)
          - Women inmates (Box 12)
        - Families and Victims (Box 12)
        - Racial Issues (Box 12)
        - Watch proceedings (Box 12)
      - Facts on death penalty (Box 12)
      - Innocence and death penalty (Box 12)
      - International perspective (Box 12)
      - Legislation
        - Michigan
          - Senate Joint Resolution F 1993 (Box 12)
          - House Joint Resolution C 1989 (Box 12)
          - Senate Joint Resolution C 1997 (Box 12)
          - House Resolution H 1999 (Box 12)
        - Tennessee and Nebraska resumptions 1999 (Box 12)
        - The Death Penalty and the Fall Elections Conference, Boston, 1998 (Box 12)
      - Michigan Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Parole (Box 12)
      - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty Project 1996-2001
        - General (Box 12)
        - Sermons, Homilies, Reflections on the Death Penalty, 1996 (Box 12)
        - Envisioning a World Without Violence study pack, 1997, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Moratorium 2000 (Box 12)
    - Moratorium on Prison Construction
      - Alternatives to incarceration, background material (Box 13)
      - Committee Against More Prisons (CAMP) (Box 13)
      - Metropolitan Correctional Center Proposal, Detroit 1977-1978, 4 folders (Box 13)
      - Michigan Coalition for Prison Alternatives 1976-1978, 3 folders (Box 13)
      - National Moratorium on Prison Construction
        - Bulletins and memoranda 1972-1977, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, related publications 1978 (Box 13)
        - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee statement 1978 (Box 13)
    - Publications on Criminal Justice
      - Series
        - "Battle Blotter" 1989 (Box 13)
        - Coalition For Prisoners Rights 1986-1991 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - Fortune News 1982-1988 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - In-Reach 1988 (Box 13)
        - Instead of Prisons, Michigan Coalition for Prison Alternatives Newsletter, 1984-1986, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Jericho 1975-1987 (scattered), 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Justicia 1983-1991 (scattered), 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Lifelines 1983-1993 (scattered), 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Marionette/Prison News Service 1986-1991 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - Mennonite Newsletter 1982-1986 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice 1984-1986 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - Outlook on Justice, New England AFSC regional office, 1983-1986 (scattered) (Box 13)
      - Individual articles and conferences
        - An End to Crime and Punishment 1976 (Box 13)
        - Bronstein, Alvin J. (Box 13)
        - Church publications on criminal justice, miscellaneous (Box 13)
        - Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants (CURE), second national convention 1989 (Box 13)
        - Friends' articles 1961, 1973, 1976, 1977, 1980 (Box 13)
        - Quaker Committee on Jails and Justice, Canada 1982, 1983 conference, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Citizens Dispute Resolution
      - Citizens Dispute Resolution; an alternative to the courts, publication of readings compiled by AFSC Ann Arbor (Box 14)
      - Grassroots Citizen Dispute Resolution Clearinghouse, Pittsburgh and Ann Arbor, grant proposals (Box 14)
      - Background material prepared by Paul Wahrhaftig, AFSC Pittsburgh 1977-1978, 4 folders (Box 14)
        (includes correspondence with the Mott Foundation)
      - Joint Grant Proposal for AFSC Grassroots Citizen Dispute Resolution Program 1977-1978 (Box 14)
        (Pittsburgh, PA and Ann Arbor, MI)
      - Proposal for Citizens' Dispute Resolution Center, Ann Arbor 1977 (Box 14)
        (proposal developed by Marc Mauer who later coordinated with Paul Wahrhaftig on a joint proposal with Pittsburgh)
    - Criminal Justice/Marc Mauer 1975-1982
      - Length of Incarceration research study/exploration 1983-1984 (Box 14)
      - Repressive Legislation 1979-1985, 1987, 3 folders (Box 14)
      - Wilmington 10 mobilization over Chavis, et al. vs. North Carolina (Box 14)
    - Criminal Justice/Penny Ryder 1982-1992
      - Community Boards 1988, 2 folders
        - General (Box 14)
        - Training Manual (Box 14)
      - Correspondence 1989, 1992 (Box 14)
      - Criminal Justice Committee 1988-1992, 4 folders (Box 14)
        (minutes, correspondence, related materials)
      - Rahway Lifers' Group 1987 (Box 14)
      - Rethinking Prisons 1990 (attendee) (Box 14)
      - "200 Years of the Penitentiary System: A Time for Change" September 13-14, 1990
        (includes correspondence and organizational materials)
        - Correspondence (Box 14)
        - Speakers, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Conference materials (Box 14)
        - Evaluation (Box 14)
    - Detroit Anti-Hunger/Youth Advocacy Center (DAH/YAC)
      - Development Memos and Minutes 1981 (Box 14)
      - Draft Counseling Proposal 1980 (Box 14)
      - Evaluation 1978-1981 (Box 14)
      - Funding and Budget 1978 (Box 14)
      - Priority: Youth Recognizing Alternative Methods in Decision-Making (P.Y.R.A.M.I.D.), Session February 22-24, 1985 (Box 14)
      - Proposal 1977-1978 (Box 14)
      - Report 1982 (Box 14)
      - Youth in Advocacy Newsletter circa 1980 (Box 14)
      - Youth Intern Proposal 1978 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Area Coordinating Committee (MACC): Community Organizing
      - Arbor Oaks Housing Task Force 1986 (Box 14)
      - Bryant Community
        - Community Center 1985-1986 (Box 14)
        - Neighborhood Alliance
          - Administration/Development 1986 (Box 14)
          - Meeting Notes December 1984-September 1987 (Box 14)
        - Proposals and Summaries 1986-1988 (Box 14)
      - Staffing 1987-1988 (Box 14)
      - Stoney Brook Subdivision 1984 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Association for the Betterment of Black Edison Employees (ABBEE) 1971-1975 (Box 14)
      - Speaker: Susan Carey 1983-1986 (Box 14)
- National and Regional Offices
  The National and Regional series documents the MAO's relationship with the national office and with the regional office in Dayton, Ohio. The National Office files include background information, publications, and material relating to the 75th anniversary of AFSC. This celebration triggered the compilation of narrative sketches of the activities of local offices and of their programs. Issues examined in this series include: Youth and Militarism (continuing the anti-war theme from the 1960s and 1970s), Affirmative Action, and more recently, Gay/Lesbian topics. The Dayton Regional Office files consist mainly of memoranda, especially those to and from Leonard Tinker. In 1985, the Dayton Regional Office merged with the Midwest Regional Office to form the Great Lakes Region office headquartered in Dayton. The records designated as Great Lakes Region include minutes, annual meeting material and information about staff retreats. This series also includes some material from the Michigan and Northern Ohio Coordinating Committee.
  - National office
    - General, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Ecology Action Project (Box 15)
    - National Community Relations Committee, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - National Legislation, Friends Committee on (Box 15)
    - Nationwide Women's Program, 5 folders (Box 15)
    - Peace Education Committee, 11 folders (Box 15)
    - Policy statements 1978-1988 (scattered) (Box 15)
    - 75th anniversary 1992 (Box 15)
      (includes photographs)
    - Nationwide Peace Education Division Executive Committee (NPEDEC)
      - Minutes and related meeting materials 1988-1992, 5 folders (Box 15)
      - History 1992 (Box 15)
        (covers period of 1925-1992)
    - Issues
      - Youth and Militarism 1989-1992 (Box 15)
      - Affirmative Action 1988-1990 (Box 15)
      - Lesbian and Gay Subcommittee 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Dayton Regional office
    - 1970-1979
      - General, 5 folders (Box 16)
      - Minutes and staff reports circa 1970-1978, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Memoranda 1973-1978, 11 folders (Box 16)
      - Don Peace Education Committee (Box 16)
      - New International Economic Order Seminar, Detroit 1979 (Box 16)
      - Regional Women's Committee, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - 1968-1984
      - American Friends Service Committee Directory 1979-1980 (Box 16)
      - Annual Meeting 1983 (Box 16)
      - Budget 1983-1984 (Box 16)
      - Budgets, Program 1979-1981 (Box 16)
      - Bulley, Julian, Reports 1968-1970 (Box 16)
      - Committee Nominations 1977 (Box 16)
      - Eastern Kentucky Project 1983 (Box 16)
      - Evaluation Process 1981 (Box 16)
      - Executive Committee Materials (Memos, Reports, Statements) January 1981-May 1983, 6 folders (Box 16)
      - Executive Committee Minutes December 1979-May 1984, 15 folders (Box 16)
      - Indiana Program Report 1983 (Box 16)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights (Affirmative Action) 1983-1984 (Box 16)
      - Louisville School Peace Education Project 1981-1983 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous Monthly Reports 1970-1973 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous Statements, Memos, and Reports 1972-1983, 7 folders (Box 16)
      - Newsletter
        - April 1975-June 1978 (Box 16)
        - Contributions and Subscriptions 1976-1977 (Box 16)
        - Production 1975 (Box 16)